Four went. Three came back. Only one of them knows what happened.
Wish You Were Here is a drama, thriller, mystery
film directed by Kieran Darcy-Smith.
Four friends lose themselves in a carefree South-East Asian holiday.
Only three come back.
Dave and Alice return home to their young family desperate for
answers about Jeremy's mysterious disappearance.
When Alice's sister Steph returns not long after, a nasty secret is
revealed about the night her boyfriend went missing.
But it is only the first of many.
Who amongst them knows what happened on that fateful night when
they were dancing under a full moon in Cambodia?
Dave Flannery, played by Joel Edgerton.
Steph McKinney, played by Teresa Palmer.
Alice Flannery, played by Felicity Price.
Jeremy King, played by Antony Starr.
Joe Canane, played by Nicholas Cassim.
Max Flannery, played by Otto Page.
Wish You Were Here is a 2012 Australian mystery drama film directed by Kieran Darcy-Smith
and starring Felicity Price, Joel Edgerton, Teresa Palmer, and Antony Starr.
Set in Cambodia and Australia, it details the aftermath of a
Southeast Asian holiday gone awry for two couples.
The film explores themes of cambodia, holiday, tourist, market, pregnant wife.
The tone is mind_bending and emotional and intense.